Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
So much for that super-powerful spell of yours, Lineface.
It seemed the Magic Knights had finally bested the Eye of the Midnight Sun's leader, until the Third Eye appeared, the Organization's three strongest members.
Oh man, looks like something didn't go as planned.
Do you know what we do to people who harm our friends?
I detest anybody who hurts Licht. I hate them.
Raya the Disloyal, Thedo the Despair, and Fauna the Hateful.
I know you'll succeed where I failed. Thank you, my friends.
The Black Bulls swiftly found themselves outmatched.
Now, let's get this over with.
Ha!
Spirit magic, salamander's breath.
But then, the captain of the green praying mantises, Jack the Ripper, Blue Rose Knight's captain, Charlotte Roselay, and Silver Eagle's captain, Nozel Silva, arrived, turning the tide of battle once again.
You're having way too much fun on your own here, Yami! You should let the rest of us in on it!
Today, time on!
Thank you.
And then, that woman turned Baro into a giant living mass of mud.
I see. It sounds to me like the Eye of the Midnight Sun was using you and your brother for their own purposes.
I guess. But we were still the ones who abducted all of those children. We were the ones who stole their magic. And so now, I'm going to take responsibility for my actions as well as my brothers.
I'll turn myself into the magic knights.
That's right. Earlier, back in the cave, Asta said something.
Good. And once you get that out of the way, you and I should be friends. With all the cool magic you can do, I bet you're going to be a pretty popular guy.
We'll be friends. I'm truly sorry.
There's hardly any point apologizing to me. Once you're done paying your dues, you're going to be Asta's friend, right?
So if I were you, I would start praying for your new buddy to win his fight and get back here in one piece.
Honestly, Asta, what are you doing out there? Finish it up already.
Asta, please stay safe.
I mean, not that it matters to me what happens to that insect, because it totally doesn't. Not in the slightest.
Why does this keep happening? And who am I even talking to?
She likes Asta too? Is that the someone special he's got his heart set on?
There's no way he'd notice me with someone like her around.
No. This isn't the time to be thinking about that. I should be getting things ready here for when they get back.
Everything else can wait. Right.
Ooh, second course. Yum.
Shame on you, getting greedy. It's not polite to hog all the interesting battles for yourself, you know.
I've got to wonder, how's it going to feel to tear them apart?
Probably not very satisfying. Kind of like ripping up a sheet of paper.
I was just about to finish him off when you morons decide to show up.
Keh, keh, keh. Yeah, I'm sure you were. Looking more ragged than usual over there.
Pfft. Me? Please.
Keh, keh, keh.
How about I work out some of my anger issues by cutting you into tiny pieces?
And there it is. You're nuts.
My sincerest apologies. Forgive me.
Keh, keh, keh. Scared now? I wasn't really going to do it.
I'd much rather wait until you're back in fighting shape before our next little skirmish.
There isn't any point if it's not a challenge.
Must we always come to get you out of trouble?
You can't even stand up, you miserable man.
Hey, it's not like that. The ground just loves my ass so much it doesn't ever want to let me go.
Don't be an idiot.
The Earth has no love for an unwashed miscreate like yourself.
Ooh, burn.
That's some mouth you got on you.
Not going to be easy to find yourself a husband, huh?
Now she's angry.
I don't need any man to marry me. The battlefield is my partner.
I get that you're a warrior woman and all, but even for you, that's pretty sad.
Does he have no regard for my feelings?
Why? Why did I have to fall for him? It's like some kind of cruel joke.
But as hard as I try, I can't keep him out of my head.
Well, I certainly can't tell him anything now.
But if I did tell him someday, what would my squad think?
You've got to be kidding me, Char!
You know he's a man, right? A gross man!
What am I doing?
Now isn't the time for this.
So, the Eye of the Midnight Sun, its leader and his top brass.
The highest ranking members of the organization that attacked our kingdom.
I won't waste this chance.
I'll bury you with my own hands.
Ooh, Nozel, you are so cool.
You just sit there and try to stay out of trouble, foreigner.
Your concern for my well-being is truly touching, oh great and mighty captain.
Hey, how do you guys think he gets his hair to do that braid thing?
He's royal, so I figure he has a servant take care of it for him, don't you think?
Honestly, I wouldn't be surprised if he had his own personal hairstylist.
I think that would qualify as the worst job ever.
What? You think he takes the time to braid his own things?
Oh yeah, he probably has lots of time on his hands. Loser.
No, on second thought, perhaps I ought to bury you before those other four.
You don't want to waste your magic on some foreigner.
Show no mercy.
Kick hit.
Oh yeah, let's do this, guys! I'm totally ready to go! We'll take these jerks down, no problem!
You won't be joining this fight.
Huh?
The captains have taken to the battlefield. Anybody who interferes now will only get in our way.
Especially a pathetic, magicless commoner like you.
Excellent. What better place to find true despair than at the end of an endless battle?
And no despair is more delicious than that of the mighty when they face certain death.
What the hell's he talking about?
Looks like we've got some rat-catching to do.
Jeez, Vero is way too excited about this fight. Sounds boring to me.
Well, whatever. I guess I can put forth some effort for Licht's sake.
And by the way, I'm calling dibs on this beautiful young lady.
When I win, you and I are going out for a drink, gorgeous.
When you win? I'm afraid we're never going to be clinking glasses then.
Briar creation magic! Corpse hunting briar tree!
Oh!
Suffering magic! Death!
Someone's eager for a fight. You're mine, Beastie.
Well, well. The praying mantis squad.
Then I'll just squash you like the insignificant bugs that you are.
You think so? Well, we'll see!
You're confident for a bug? Fine!
Let's see you smile while I'm ripping you limp from leg!
Go back home!
I've been waiting for this. Finally.
Mercury magic! Silver spears!
Yet another foolish person attempting to harm Licht.
For that, you'll die.
Looks like the salamander girl's flames are melting your mercury.
You want to swap opponent, silver boy?
I don't think so. Those flames are hardly enough to best me.
You have no idea what I had to do to get where I am.
You're the also who haste tree.
Good luck!
Bloody guts!
Run now!
It shithcl
All this magic flying around, it looks like some kind of natural disaster.
I can't see through all this dust.
Jeez, they're really fighting hard.
Better be careful, Jack. You talk a good game, but you cut it kind of close.
Looks like Charlotte's doing well, though.
And those L's bangs haven't budged at all.
You can see?
Remember, Ki? I can sense them.
Yeah.
Venral, you ready?
For what, sir?
You've been resting up for a while now. You ought to have enough mana for a spatial spell.
You mean we're leaving? Sure, I'm ready. Let the other captains handle this. We can just...
The Magic Knight captains are as powerful as I expected them to be.
However, they are no match for the Third Eye.
Our people are much loved by the mana of this world, and that is why there must be some mistake.
How could an ordinary human, one who's magicless, clearly shunned by the mana, possess that grimoire?
I must retrieve it from his unworthy hands at once.
He's been weakened, but I'm not gonna risk letting him get away.
Ah, yes. I expected this from you.
He's countering?
Not good. Look out, sir!
Oh, dear.
You misjudged our boss, I see.
I'll end you this time.
Finishingly.
You're going after the boss, too, aren't you?
All right. Bring it!
How did he get over there?
It shouldn't have been possible in all this confusion.
That's the kind of thing you can do when you learn to read key.
No one noticed.
No one.
None of us could sense this boy.
Because he has no magic.
We're gonna get you this time!
Thanks for trusting that I was gonna take one last shot at you while I had the chance.
As for me, I put my trust in our magicless freak here.
My magic is never giving up!
Gotcha!
So what'd you think about my magic-free smash attack?
You trying to take all the credit, kid?
Sorry, Captain.
Not bad. You really pushed past your limits that time.
Thank you!
Where's Lyft?
Oh, no!
Eyes forward, PC!
That little runt!
He left us to the dust!
Kid!
So much for getting all the glory!
We're magic knight captains!
We can't fall behind!
It's up to us to take care of the rest!
Captain Yami?
Wonder if any more of their friends are gonna show up.
I guess we'll see.
It would be so cool!
Now's your chance to finish him
while the other captains keep the rest of them busy!
Hmm.
He's glowing!
What the...
No!
When that brat hit licked with his anti-magic attack,
it broke the spell of sealing that was cast on him!
That's not good.
That power had been set aside for a day still to come.
This cannot be!
Why do you have that grimoire?
Why do you wield them?
The Demon Slayer Sword
and the Demon Dweller Sword?
What's he saying?
Those swords belong to the Master!
The Master...
According to our intel,
the Master is the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Does this mean he isn't the Master?
You keep saying this crap!
Well, I'm sick of it!
It doesn't matter who this Master guy is, okay?
This grimoire and these swords are mine!
I don't care if they're all beat up!
Now quit with all the accusations!
They're not yours!
Give them back!
That grimoire could never belong to you!
The Master's grimoire could never be yours, filthy human!
Oh boy!
What now, Captain?
Things aren't looking so good, huh?
Well, this should be fun!
Damn, no!
No way!
It absorbed my separating magic like it was nothing!
That's an enormous mass of pure magic power!
If he releases it, we're all dead!
It'll destroy everything in the surrounding area!
But what do we do?
Even we cannot stop this!
How much mana is he channeling?
He's been holding back!
He could have obliterated us anytime he wanted to!
I should have never come on this stupid mission!
Actually, scratch that!
I should never have joined this squad to begin with!
Stop running your mouth!
Nobody wants to hear it!
Besides, this could be our chance!
Just think of all the limits we could push past!
We'll be up against some real power!
Let's go!
No way!
Seriously!
Have you people gone crazy here?
Hey!
Shut up and pull it together, Fen'Roll!
I'm still your superior!
My magic's not fully recovered yet!
Can I reflect his strike with what I have?
That's too bad!
I'll need a rain check on that drink!
His body isn't going to hold out much longer!
We need to hurry!
Trinity!
Sealing!
Magic!
They mean to seal away that?
All that magic!
Incredible!
You pushed yourself just a little too hard this time, Likt.
We've got you.
Now get some rest.
It will be all right.
For now.
It's time to go, Vaultie.
Our boss is feeling a bit under the weather.
So we're gonna have to call it a day.
We may have lost to you people this time around.
Just wait.
I promise when we meet again, I won't leave until you've tasted true despair.
We carnivores live to feast on bottom-feeding vermin like you.
The next time we meet, you'll draw your last breath.
Remember, wherever you go, the eye of the midnight sun is watching.
That much magic power.
And they were able to seal it with a single spell.
So then, they were toying with us.
The third eye.
Not only do they have a tremendous amount of mana,
they are singularly skilled at using it.
Much loved by the mana is right.
Kier, kier, kier.
I'd like another chance to rip them apart.
We let them get away.
But it won't happen again.
I will avenge you.
I swear it.
So, did we win?
It's less that we won, and more like the other guys ran off.
From where I'm standing, them running off like that is as good as a win.
Besides, Beast Boy said they lost.
Kier, kier, kier, kier, kier.
Kier, kier, kier.
You heard the captain.
We won.
Yep, we totally did.
You didn't do anything.
Dude, chill out.
We did it!
Yummy, we're waiting.
Is there something you'd like to say to us?
I'm hungry.
Kier, kier, kier.
I don't care about your stomach.
I thought a thank you might be in order.
What would you have done if the other captains and I hadn't shown up?
You can bet your scythe I wouldn't have let them get away.
I would have taken them all down.
Kier, kier, kier.
You don't really think that would have been possible.
You foolish man.
Fighting enemies that strong alone would be nothing short of reckless.
Would it kill you to be nice for once, woman?
Still, the idea that he would take on all of them by himself
I didn't fall in love with him for nothing.
You should try to control that tongue of yours.
Otherwise, you're gonna die single.
I told you, I don't care!
The battlefield is my husband!
Worry about finding your own partner and leave me be!
I'll make a deal with you, Charlotte.
If we're both still single when we're old and gray,
we can look after each other.
What? You're joking.
Who would want to be with someone like you?
Why can't I just be honest and tell him how I really feel?
Asta's down.
Push past his limits and then some.
All right.
Get him healed up.
Go on.
Who, me?
Yeah, make yourself useful.
Like I've been doing all day, you mean?
Oh, shut up!
I'll have to remember this one.
Asta, was it?
They sure got the best of you this time, huh?
Sorry, Licht.
Well, you can rest a bit now.
I detest them.
Well, that was a pathetic showing.
And you're our strongest members.
What did you say?
Just, what do we do next?
The Wizard King will get a report about Licht.
And soon, he'll start pushing even harder.
On top of that, York and Catherine are still in custody.
If they talk, the Magic Knights could find this place.
They could even discover Licht's true identity.
Easy.
Ray-D's does have a point.
It's too soon.
We don't want to put all our cards on the table.
Well, not yet anyway.
Okay.
What to do, what to do.
I don't really want to go,
but it doesn't appear that we have much of a choice.
What a pain.
Hmm.
acting weird. Honestly, why did I have to fall for a man who smokes like a chimney, has the manners
of a boar, and absolutely does not look 28? I just want to wrap him up in briars. Yummy!
Hey, Char, what were you saying about Captain Yami?
I wasn't saying anything, and don't call me Captain, call me Char! Wait, scratch that,
reverse it! I swear I heard you say something about briars, too.
You, briars? Of course, briars! I was just thinking about how much I'd like to tie Yami up with some of
those, you know? Okay, I get it. Now you're talking about torturing him! Wow, if you want to do something
like that, you must really hate Captain Yami a lot, huh, Char? Yes, I hate him so much! Yes, I mean,
he is a man! Who'd ever want to see that guy's ugly face? Exactly! Not even his face! Right! And I'd like
to smack him with a briar whip! Oh, why can't I just be honest and tell him how I really feel?
Hurting licked like that. How despicable. I will never forgive the Magic Knights. Black Clover,
page 38. The Magic Knight Captain Conference. Clover Kingdom, the end is near.
So, I was just the individual
and I was looking for it when I came in the middle and the middle finally came!
So,
try it,
cause it's absolutely nice!
The Magic Knight of the Magic Knight
is always looking for internet access.
So,
tell the Magic Knight of the Magic Knight and the Magic Knight was so